SEBASTIÁN GIRALDO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

During my time in the industry, I have had the opportunity to work on a variety of exciting projects, from mobile application development to building websites and business management systems.

This has allowed me to gain a great deal of hands-on experience in different areas of programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER & UI/UX

Cattleya - Sports

November 2022 - Actuality

Currently developing an Ecommerce, whose purpose is to improve the sales of the company, with online payment methods such as Stripe, Mercado Pago and PayPal.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER & UI/UX

Freelancer

June 2022 - November 2022

Working as a Freelancer for a hairdresser and hair extensions company, developing a Landing Page.

BACKEND DEVELOPER & UI/UX

Open Bootcamp - OpenWeekApps

August 2022 - December 2022

Team work, Backend, Frontend and Design development activities. I developed an API in collaboration with other developers and I was also in charge of the design of the Apps that all teams were assigned for development.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER & UI/UX

Innova Ingenieria Integral

August 2021 - August 2022

Full Stack for 1 year, developing a Web App for families with people with disabilities, helping and improving the family nucleus with the person.

CONTACT

+57 3152058712

Colombia - Tolima

social-portfolio.vercel.app/

EDUCATION

January 2020 - August 2022Computer technologist Software engineering in SENA

LANGUAGES

English-A2/B1

SKILLS

Agile Methodologies Critical/logical thinking Ability to work as part of a team Initiative and active learning Figma, Photoshop, Illustration

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript
React, Vite, Next, Typescript
Nodejs, MySQL, MongoDB, Agile
Git, GitHub, Jira, Bitbucket, Trello, Azure
Tailwindcss, Chakra, Bootstrap, Bulma
Semantic UI, AntDesign, Flexbox